<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Data Science Portfolio</title><link>https://adarshkrishnan.com/</link><description>Recent content on Data Science Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adarshkrishnan.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Résumé | Adarsh Krishnan</title><link>https://adarshkrishnan.com/experiences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adarshkrishnan.com/experiences/</guid><description>Profile Data Scientist with 4 years of experience driving business impact through data analytics, machine learning, and automation. Proficient in Python, SQL, and A/B testing with a strong grounding in causal inference. Adept at translating complex data into actionable insights to support strategic decision-making across product, business, and operational teams.
Note: Currently on a Skilled Worker Visa and would require Visa sponsorship for a new role.
Skills Programming &amp;amp; Databases Python SQL C++ Streamlit Snowflake Data Science &amp;amp; ML Machine Learning Statistical Analysis A/B Experimentation Causal Inference Data Visualisation Tools &amp;amp; Platforms AWS Tableau Power BI Fivetran Git Docker Linux Professional Stakeholder Engagement Technical Presentations Project Management Experience Data Consultant STONEHAVEN | London, UK | Jul 2023 - Present Automated data pipelines from S3 to Snowflake using AWS Lambda and Fivetran, cutting manual data processing effort by 90%.</description></item><item><title>What Is Bioinformatics</title><link>https://adarshkrishnan.com/blogs/what-is-bioinformatics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adarshkrishnan.com/blogs/what-is-bioinformatics/</guid><description>Bioinformatics combines biology and computing to analyze biological data. This introductory post briefly outlines the field and points to resources for further study.</description></item><item><title>QSAR Modeling of Acetylcholinesterase Inhibitors</title><link>https://adarshkrishnan.com/projects/acetylcholinesterase/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adarshkrishnan.com/projects/acetylcholinesterase/</guid><description>A small study using QSAR modeling and docking to explore inhibitors of human acetylcholinesterase.</description></item><item><title>How to master Streamlit for Data Science</title><link>https://adarshkrishnan.com/blogs/how-to-master-streamlit-for-data-science/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adarshkrishnan.com/blogs/how-to-master-streamlit-for-data-science/</guid><description>Streamlit is a lightweight framework that makes it easy to build interactive data apps using only Python. This brief article points to resources for mastering Streamlit when starting out in data science.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://adarshkrishnan.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://adarshkrishnan.com/about/</guid><description>Hi there! I&amp;rsquo;m a data scientist who loves to explore the world of data and share my findings with others. This website is my personal space to showcase my projects, write about my data science journey, and connect with like-minded people. I hope you find something interesting here!</description></item></channel></rss>